Bunnies are going to Broadcast Asia in Singapore! 🐰 - Let's dive into your future success with bunny.net🚀

x

    * Products
    * [
        
        CDN
        
        Lightning-fast global CDN](#)
        * CDN
        * [
            
            Bunny CDN](https://bunny.net/cdn/)
        * [
            
            CDN Features](https://bunny.net/cdn/features/)
        * [
            
            SafeHop™](https://bunny.net/cdn/safehop/)
        * [
            
            Perma-Cache](https://bunny.net/cdn/perma-cache/)
        * [
            
            CDN Pricing](https://bunny.net/pricing/cdn/)
    * [
        
        Stream
        
        A better way to deliver online videos](#)
        * Stream
        * [
            
            Bunny Stream](https://bunny.net/stream/)
        * [
            
            Media Player](https://bunny.net/stream/cdn-player/)
        * [
            
            Media Cage](https://bunny.net/stream/media-cage-video-content-protection/)
        * [
            
            Enteprise Multi-DRM](https://bunny.net/stream/media-cage-enterprise-multi-drm-digital-rights-management/)
        * [
            
            Transcribe AI](https://bunny.net/stream/transcribe-ai/)
        * [
            
            Stream Pricing](https://bunny.net/pricing/stream/)
    * [
        
        Storage
        
        The world's fastest cloud storage](#)
        * Storage
        * [
            
            Bunny Storage](https://bunny.net/storage/)
        * [
            
            SSD Storage](https://bunny.net/storage/ssd/)
        * [
            
            Storage Pricing](https://bunny.net/pricing/storage/)
    * [
        
        Optimizer
        
        Powerful image processing & optimization](#)
        * Optimizer
        * [
            
            Bunny Optimizer](https://bunny.net/optimizer/)
        * [
            
            Dynamic Image Processing](https://bunny.net/optimizer/transform-api/)
        * [
            
            Optimizer Pricing](https://bunny.net/pricing/optimizer/)
    * [
        
        DNS
        
        Next-generation DNS routing](#)
        * DNS
        * [
            
            Bunny DNS](https://bunny.net/dns/)
        * [
            
            DNS Pricing](https://bunny.net/pricing/dns/)
    * [
        
        Fonts
        
        First privacy oriented fonts](#)
        * Fonts
        * [
            
            Bunny Fonts](https://bunny.net/fonts/)
        * [
            
            Fonts API](https://fonts.bunny.net/)
    * Working on a bigger project?

    * Solutions
    * [
        
        By Need](https://bunny.net/stream/)
        * By Need
        * [
            
            Video and Streaming](#)
            * Video and Streaming
            * [Video Delivery
                
                Deliver the best video experience.](https://bunny.net/solutions/video-delivery/)
            * [Media Cage
                
                Keep your videos secured and safe.](https://bunny.net/stream/media-cage-video-content-protection/)
            * [Enterprise Multi-DRM
                
                Hollywood grade video protection.](https://bunny.net/stream/media-cage-enterprise-multi-drm-digital-rights-management/)
            * [Transcribe AI
                
                Generate captions with a single click](https://bunny.net/stream/transcribe-ai/)
        * [
            
            Storage and Delivery](#)
            * Storage and Delivery
            * [Game Delivery
                
                Best Gaming experience at any scale.](https://bunny.net/solutions/gaming-cdn/)
            * [Software Distribution
                
                Fastest storage for fastest downloads.](https://bunny.net/solutions/software-distribution/)
        * [
            
            Website Performance](#)
            * Website Performance
            * [Website Acceleration
                
                Supercharge your Website](https://bunny.net/solutions/website-acceleration/)
            * [Permanent Caching
                
                Permanently store files on the edge.](https://bunny.net/cdn/perma-cache/)
            * [Dynamic Image Processing
                
                Say goodbye to slow loading images](https://bunny.net/optimizer/transform-api/)
            * [Wordpress CDN
                
                #1 Wordpress CDN on the market](https://bunny.net/solutions/wordpress-cdn/)
        * [
            
            Security and Protection](#)
            * Security and Protection
            * [CDN Security
                
                No more downtimes ever again](https://bunny.net/solutions/cdn-security/)
            * [DDoS Protection
                
                DDoS Protection at the Network Edge](https://bunny.net/network/ddos-protection/)
    * [
        
        By Industry](#)
        * By Industry
        * [
            
            Streaming](#)
            * Streaming
            * [Video Delivery
                
                Improve your video delivery.](https://bunny.net/solutions/video-delivery/)
            * [Transcribe AI
                
                Generate captions with a single click](https://bunny.net/stream/transcribe-ai/)
        * [
            
            Ecommerce](#)
            * Ecommerce
            * [Website Acceleration
                
                Supercharge your website](https://bunny.net/solutions/website-acceleration/)
            * [Image Optimization
                
                Optimize and compress images](https://bunny.net/optimizer/transform-api/)
            * [WordPress CDN
                
                Improve your loading speeds](https://bunny.net/solutions/wordpress-cdn/)
            * [CDN Security
                
                Take control of your security](https://bunny.net/solutions/cdn-security/)
        * [
            
            Gaming](#)
            * Gaming
            * [Gaming CDN
                
                Deliver best Gaming experience](https://bunny.net/solutions/gaming-cdn/)
            * [Software Distribution
                
                Supercharge your global downloads](https://bunny.net/solutions/software-distribution/)
    * See how bunny.net helped other companies reach the next leve!.

    * Resources
    * [
        
        About bunny.net
        
        Learn more about our goals, values and mission](https://bunny.net/about/)
    * [
        
        Bunny Careers
        
        Help us shape the future of the internet](https://bunny.net/careers/)
    * [
        
        Bunny Blog
        
        Keep up to date with our announcements](https://bunny.net/blog/)
    * [
        
        Super Bunnies™
        
        The best support in CDN business](https://bunny.net/super-bunnies-cdn-support/)
    * [
        
        Bunny Academy
        
        Learn about networking, cyber security and how the internet works.](https://bunny.net/academy/)
    * [
        
        Contact Us
        
        Get in touch with bunny.net team](https://bunny.net/contact/)
    * 

    * Products
    * [Bunny CDN
        
        Lightning-fast global CDN](https://bunny.net/cdn/)
    * [
        
        Bunny Stream
        
        A better way to deliver online videos](https://bunny.net/stream/)
    * [Bunny Storage
        
        The world's fastest cloud storage](https://bunny.net/storage/)
    * [Bunny Optimizer
        
        Powerful image processing & optimization](https://bunny.net/optimizer/)
    * [Bunny DNS
        
        Next-generation DNS routing](https://bunny.net/dns/)
    * [Bunny Fonts
        
        First privacy oriented fonts](https://bunny.net/fonts/)
    * Working on a bigger project?

    * Solutions
    * [
        
        By Need](https://bunny.net/stream/)
        * By Need
        * [
            
            Video and Streaming](#)
            * Video and Streaming
            * [Video Delivery
                
                Deliver the best video experience.](https://bunny.net/solutions/video-delivery/)
            * [Media Cage
                
                Keep your videos secured and safe.](https://bunny.net/stream/media-cage-video-content-protection/)
        * [
            
            Storage and Delivery](#)
            * Storage and Delivery
            * [Game Delivery
                
                Best Gaming experience at any scale.](https://bunny.net/solutions/gaming-cdn/)
            * [Software Distribution
                
                Fastest storage for fastest downloads.](https://bunny.net/solutions/software-distribution/)
        * [
            
            Website Performance](#)
            * Website Performance
            * [Website Acceleration
                
                Supercharge your Website](https://bunny.net/solutions/website-acceleration/)
            * [Permanent Caching
                
                Permanently store files on the edge.](https://bunny.net/cdn/perma-cache/)
            * [Dynamic Image Processing
                
                Say goodbye to slow loading images](https://bunny.net/optimizer/transform-api/)
            * [Wordpress CDN
                
                #1 Wordpress CDN on the market](https://bunny.net/solutions/wordpress-cdn/)
        * [
            
            Security and Protection](#)
            * Security and Protection
            * [CDN Security
                
                No more downtimes ever again](https://bunny.net/solutions/cdn-security/)
            * [DDoS Protection
                
                DDoS Protection at the Network Edge](https://bunny.net/network/ddos-protection/)
    * [
        
        By Industry](#)
        * By Industry
        * [
            
            Streaming](#)
            * Streaming
            * [Video Delivery
                
                Improve your video delivery.](https://bunny.net/solutions/video-delivery/)
        * [
            
            Ecommerce](#)
            * Ecommerce
            * [Website Acceleration
                
                Supercharge your website](https://bunny.net/solutions/website-acceleration/)
            * [Image Optimization
                
                Optimize and compress images](https://bunny.net/optimizer/transform-api/)
            * [WordPress CDN
                
                Improve your loading speeds](https://bunny.net/solutions/wordpress-cdn/)
            * [CDN Security
                
                Take control of your security](https://bunny.net/solutions/cdn-security/)
        * [
            
            Gaming](#)
            * Gaming
            * [Gaming CDN
                
                Deliver best Gaming experience](https://bunny.net/solutions/gaming-cdn/)
            * [Software Distribution
                
                Supercharge your global downloads](https://bunny.net/solutions/software-distribution/)
    * See how bunny.net helped other companies reach the next leve!.

    * Resources
    * [
        
        About bunny.net
        
        Learn more about our goals, values and mission](https://bunny.net/about/)
    * [
        
        Bunny Careers
        
        Help us shape the future of the internet](https://bunny.net/careers/)
    * [
        
        Bunny Blog
        
        Keep up to date with our announcements](https://bunny.net/blog/)
    * [
        
        Bunny Academy
        
        Easy way to learn how the internet works](https://bunny.net/academy/)
    * [Super Bunnies™
        
        The best support In the CDN business](https://bunny.net/super-bunnies-cdn-support/)
    * [
        
        Contact Us
        
        Get in touch with bunny.net team](https://bunny.net/contact/)

Privacy & Data Policy
=====================

How we're protecting your data
------------------------------

At bunny.net, we take data privacy very seriously. We want to be completely transparent about the information that we store, how we use it and how we keep it secure.

Data Policy
-----------

**What data do we collect, and how do we collect it?** bunny.net collects the following data, when you sign up for a bunny.net account, we ask for your full name, email address, and postal address, this allows us to provide you with our services. This will also sometimes be used to verify your payment details when you top up your account, you can find out more about our third-party payment gateways below.

bunny.net does not share any personal data with any third party except information required to function correctly. This will only be collected from users when registering an account and only if the user enters the data voluntarily. We do not store any personal information about your visits that is not entered voluntarily.

By registering at bunny.net, it shall be deemed that the user gives consent to the processing of personal data relating to him or her. Registration/creating a user account without submitting the requested data is impossible. The report will not function past the trial if the data subject does not complete the registration process. The provision of personal information is a contractual requirement, as well as a requirement necessary to enter into a contract. Should the data subject not provide the requested data, the business relationship with bunny.net cannot be established, and consequently, services performed.

bunny.net is processing data based on:

1\. The data subject\`s given consent to the processing of her data.  
2\. Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is a party and is also necessary to take steps toward the conclusion of a business relationship.  
3\. Processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which bunny.net is subject. The latter refers to the data that bunny.net is obliged to provide or keep under the tax and accounting regulation.

How long we retain your data
----------------------------

The personal data shall be removed after the contract/deregistration of the user\`s account expires. Should there be any outstanding liabilities, bunny.net shall keep necessary personal data to exercise our legal rights until the payment of outstanding amounts. The personal data listed in tax and accounting documents shall be kept for the period under the tax and accounting regulation.

How we protect your data
------------------------

We make a great effort to ensure the security of your data using the latest encryption methods and never storing information such as your passwords in plain text. We also use encrypted traffic and communication in all critical parts of our system to ensure the safety of your data. Your credit card details are never stored on our servers for security reasons. Instead, we use one of the most secure payment providers, BrainTree, to process and store your billing information safely.

Withdrawal of consent
---------------------

The data subject has a reserved right to withdraw consent at any time regarding data processing without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. The effectiveness of such a withdrawal shall extend only to the data where the processing is based on the consent of the data subject, but not on the data where processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is a party, or the data that is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the bunny.net is subject.

The right to lodge a complaint
------------------------------

Every data subject has the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of his or her habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement if the data subject considers that the processing of personal data relating to him or her infringes GDPR.

Other Rights
------------

The data subject has a reserved right to request from bunny.net access to and rectify or personal erasure data or restrict processing concerning the data subject. For exercising such rights, refer to support@bunny.net.

OpenAI
------

When utilizing the Fluffee chat, our system leverages the OpenAI ChatGPT API to provide you with responses. Please note that this process entails the utilization of your data in order to assist you in resolving your queries.

Anonymous non-personal data policy
----------------------------------

In order to improve users with the best website experience, we may collect some anonymous information about users visiting and interacting with our website such as the name of their browser, pages visited, and points of interest on the website based on mouse heatmap technology as outlined below using a completely anonymous service called Matomo.

### Non-Personal Data Only

We use a service called Matomo that strictly only tracks non-personal data that does not include any user identifiable information.

### 100% Anonymous

The data collected is not tied to any account or user and is 100% anonymous and used strictly for statistical reasons and to improve user experience.

### Not Shared

All anonymous data is kept by us, so there are no chances of a third party tying your unique ID and behavior to any personal profile.

### Web browser cookie policy

Our website might use cookies in order to operate normally, allowing you to log into the dashboard and provide us with anonymous statistics about your visit to help us enhance the user experience of our website.

We have carefully designed and overviewed our cookie usage in order to make sure we never store any kind of personal information or information that would allow anyone to identify you.

Sharing your personal data
--------------------------

During a payment process, we might pass your billing information such as credit card details, IP, and email to a service called BrainTree that will then use this for secure payment processing on our behalf.

Savio will receive your account information (such as Email, Name, and Company Name) this will only be shared when you submit a feature request, ensuring a more tailored and efficient service.

During a payment process, we might pass your billing information such as IP and email address to a service called Coinify that will then use this for secure payment processing on our behalf.

When posting a comment on our blog or knowledge base, your provided information is shared with a service called Disqus that we use to provide users the ability to leave comments under our articles.

During signup, we might share your current IP, browser user agent, browser language, and email address provided during signup to a third party service MaxMind that we use to detect and prevent credit card fraud.

Salesforce will receive billing, consumption, and service usage details. No zone configuration or end customer data will be shared, but communications with bunny.net may be processed by Salesforce.

After signing up for an account, we might share your name and email address with a service called SendGrid that we use to process and send email notifications related to your bunny.net account.

Tableau will receive your personal, billing and account consumption details such as zone count, usage, or other metrics to help us improve the service, but no zone configuration or end customer data will be shared.

When interacting with our support team or using the website support widget, information such as your email address and name might be passed to a service called ZenDesk that we use for managing our support.

MixPanel will receive your personal account details as well as information on how you use our services within the dashboard to help us improve the service, but no zone configuration or end customer data will be shared.

When you register an account with us, Active Campaign will receive your personal, billing, and account consumption information, including details like the number of zones and usage, and other relevant metrics. However, we will not share any information regarding zone configurations or data related to your end customers.

This privacy policy is subject to change without prior notice. It was last updated on 10/08/2023.

If you require more information or have any questions, feel free to contact us at: support@bunny.net

Address: BunnyWay d.o.o., Dunajska cesta 165, 1000 Ljubljana, Slovenia

Start Your 14 Day Free Trial
----------------------------

Join over 40.000+ satisfied customers already using bunny.net

No credit card required – Complete Registration in under 2 minutes.

#### [bunny.net](https://bunny.net/)

#### Products

#### Developers

#### Support

#### Big traffic? Talk to Sales

Working on a big project?  
Let our experts help you out.

#### Stay up to date with bunny.net

Follow us on social media for special promotions and important news.

~ Making the internet hop faster!

2024 All Rights Reserved © BunnyWay d.o.o.
